Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Breathe, come on.
It's getting worse.
She has an active imagination.
She's really scared.
I know. But there's no signs of anybody
coming in so I don't know what we can do.
She wants to move back.
That's it, isn't it? This is part of that?
- I don't think she's making this up.
- It's not an option.
This is the only place we can afford,
and it's close to my job.
- Uh, we could move back.
- We can't. They're still looking for us.
You shouldn't have borrowed from them.
It was the only option.
- You should've...
- What? Just let you die?
There was no miracle match
coming to that hospital.
- It could have happened!
- It was the only way.
We could've found another way.
I found a way, and you're alive.
This is a small town.
They're not going to look for us here.
Hopefully, maybe, you can find a job.
Pay them back. I don't know how...
...but we will.
Hello?
Come out.
I don't want any trouble.
Just...
...so just come out!
Maybe you can help your father
unpack in the basement.
Do I have to?
No.
But it would be nice to get everything
in order so we can enjoy the house.
Will that do it?
Hey, don't worry about it.
You can help out another night.
It's all mine tonight.
Once school starts,
you'll like it better here.
I don't like it here.
Give it time. You'll make
new friends once school starts.
We have to make it work.
Hopefully your father gets a job.
Megan, did you just say something?
Rob! Rob! Rob!
There was somebody there.
I checked everywhere.
All the doors are locked.
Maybe it was a mouse.
It wasn't a mouse. Too big, and that sound.
Well, it's an old house, so...
- Megan didn't say anything?
- No, she didn't notice anything.
So... so out of it for that minute.
She seems out of it a lot.
Maybe just the stress of a new school.
Probably.
Bitch is mine!
What are you doing?
Other...
...There was a...
Bitch is mine!
- We are both tired and stressed.
- I didn't imagine it.
So some creature running around,
perched on the walls. Is that is?
- You saw something too.
- I thought I did, but no faces.
It's just stress, probably.
Something doesn't feel right here.
So you want to go back too?
Well, I guess Megan is getting to you.
- I didn't say that. But it's not...
- I have to go to work.
We can talk later.
- What's happening to me?
- Nothing. You just need to rest.
I feel so tired all the time.
It'll pass.
I'm scared.
There's nothing to be scared about.
She's coming for me.
What are you talking about?
I can't see her clearly, but she's coming.
Nobody's coming for you.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I feel her every night.
Look.
If anybody's coming in here,
we'll catch them. So don't worry.
I'm on watch all night.
Good night, Megan.
Good night.
Megan, I'm going to go wake up
your mom. Can you get the coffee going?
Oh, hey, honey, it's just me.
Don't be scared.
Wait. You?
What?
- Weren't you just downstairs?
- No.
We must have had a blackout.
All the clocks reset.
- It was fine last night.
- I thought it thundered.
- You see that?
- What?
There.
Play it again.
I turned.
Something moved.
It was my shadow.
Maybe.
Hey.
- Got something for you.
- It's not my birthday yet.
I know. But I saw this at the antique store.
It's an advance gift.
- It's beautiful.
- What's beautiful?
This.
Where did you get that?
Got it at an antique store.
It's beautiful, right?
Open it.
- Love that picture.
- Thanks, Dad.
Oh! Oh, you're strong.
Going to mess up my new kidney.
- Sorry.
- Just kidding.
I know things have been rough,
but everything's going to be okay.
All right?
Right.
Hope so.
Time for school.
What store did you say you got that at again?
At the...
What does it matter?
It doesn't. Just curious.
Hi.
Uh, sorry to bother you. I'm Skip.
This is my partner, Helena.
- Do we know each other?
- No. We were just...
How can I help you?
Well, it's, um,
how we can help you, actually.
- Your daughter's in danger.
- What do you know about my daughter?
Your daughter is in danger,
and I can tell by your face you know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Your daughter is being targeted,
and we're here to help you.
- Please, Robert, hear us out.
- How do you know my name?
Listen, we followed the signs to you.
The ones before you.
The birth records. The whole profile.
It's not from the world of the living.
Her birthday is in three days.
That's all the time you have.
You're crazy. Both of you.
Now get out of here.
You don't have much time left. Please.
- All right, get out of here, now!
- Okay, okay, okay. We're sorry.
We're go... we're going, we're going.
Just, um, take my card.
- Please.
- Go!
Call me.
Are you really going to stay down here again?
I need to.
What are you doing?
Backup, in case the power goes out again.
It won't. It's supposed to be clear tonight.
I hope it is!
Susan! Susan!
Susan!
Susan.
Hey, Susan.
- You should go to the doctor.
- It's okay. It's just surface cuts.
It might get infected.
They won't.
Well, we have to report this.
Whoever did this is still out there.
What are we going to report?
Someone carved crosses on my back...
- ...and we didn't see him?
- That's the truth.
We can't afford for people
to think we are crazy.
- No, they won't.
- They will.
People don't hire crazies.
I can't lose this job.
- Then what can we do?
- I don't know!
Cameras.
I had another bad dream.
- Father Mullins, thank you for coming.
- Well, I'll be happy to help if I can.
Have you... have you taken her
to see a doctor again?
Yes. And they still say she's fine.
Well...
...I don't see what it is I can do.
I mean, what I see here is...
...it's disturbing. But...
...but that's all it is.
And I think that maybe you
should seek professional help.
No, Father. She's normal.
All of this is recent.
She's not crazy.
No, dear, I'm not suggesting she's crazy.
I just think that you'd benefit
by a real professional opinion.
If you just could take a look at her.
Well, of course I can, and I will.
But I just don't see
what good it's going to do.
It just would be great if you did.
She's stayed in bed since yesterday.
She's really out of it.
Megan?
Megan, this is Father Mullins.
He's just here to check on you.
Megan, how are you feeling, dear?
I'm tired.
Why are you tired, dear?
No reason.
Well, they also said
that you told them that...
"...she" was coming to get you.
Yes, she is.
Hmm.
And, uh, who is she?
I don't know.
Well, um...
...where does she live?
I don't know.
But you do.
What?
She lives in the same place
you take young boys to.
Maybe you want to try a little girl instead.
- Megan! Megan!
- Oh!
- Megan! Megan! Megan!
- Megan!
Help me.
Megan. Megan.
Father, please help us!
I have not done anything.
- Maybe some impure thoughts.
- We're not judging you.
- But I took an oath.
- But you haven't done anything, Father...
- ...and that's all that matters.
- I don't know how...
...or what this thing is.
Something is happening to her,
and it's not medical.
So, what, you think this is a possession?
Somebody else said that.
- Who?
- Look, I...
...I'll speak with my superiors and see
if there's anything that we can do, okay?
Thank you, Father.
I am sorry. Very sorry.
It wasn't her.
No, it wasn't.
She's just sick.
I understand that this
must be very hard to process...
...but she is being possessed.
Possessed?
Is that what you want us to believe?
Yes.
What other explanation do you have?
I don't know.
You called us.
Because you're out of options, right?
The priest.
Did you call the police the first time?
All we had then was that the intruder
appeared to be Megan.
We can't afford the attention.
We're new here.
There's a prophecy that on
the 18th birthday of a girl...
...born to parents out of wedlock...
...that girl will serve as a vessel
for the entrance into this world...
...of a demon.
We were young.
But we did the right thing getting married.
I'm not judging you.
I'm sorry, we're not judging you.
This is how we found you.
Additionally, the girl would be living
in a home with a past like the future.
What does that mean?
A girl died in your home a while ago.
What happened to her?
She was killed.
They never found the killer.
Oh, my God.
We're sorry you had to find out
this way, but it's best you know.
Wait.
- Is that her?
- Yes!
The Willow girl.
- Where did you get this?
- Found it in the basement.
- You gave it to Megan!
- I didn't know.
She's in great danger.
You said a house with a past like the future.
Does that mean Megan will be killed?
If she possesses her...
...she will be dead in spirit.
This is crazy. I can't believe you.
She's going to...
she's going to be 18 in two days.
Please, just let us try to help you.
- What can you do?
- Stop the demon before it takes her over.
Who is this demon?
The demon's name...
...her name...
...is Abyzou.
Now, she couldn't conceive a child...
...to carry on her legacy,
so the point when a girl...
...becomes a woman...
...is the point
when she can fulfill her goal...
...to enter this world again.
This is crazy.
There's no other explanation.
It's you.
Open the door or I'm going to call the cops.
Go away!
There's something happening to my daughter.
You made a deal.
I was desperate. I promise
I will pay you back the money.
Just leave her alone.
It isn't with me.
You didn't make a deal with me.
That's bullshit. This "selling
her soul" nonsense. It's bullshit.
I didn't believe that.
You took the money...
...and she made it happen.
Abyzou.
Your daughter.
She was killed.
Was it her? Abyzou?
I don't know what you're talking about.
The locket you tried to give me
for my daughter.
My husband found that in my house.
No.
That's impossible.
Please, you know more. Please help me.
I was asked to make an offer.
That's all.
I can't help you.
I accepted the money.
That's it. The rest is bullshit!
The offer was real.
I'm going to call the cops.
If you call the cops,
what are you going to tell them?
That you made a deal with me
to sell your daughter's soul?
Is Abyzou real?
Yes.
What can I do?
You made a deal.
God help you.
Please tell me what I can do.
Help me!
Help me.
Uh, holy water.
You might see some things
tonight you don't want to see.
We already have.
Tonight is Megan's birthday,
and so the demon will most likely...
...take on a more physical form
to try to take her over.
This is our best chance to stop it.
You have to be strong,
and listen only to me and Helena.
I'll take first watch.
You guys get some rest.
I'll wake you up later.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
Skip. Skip.
Helena?
I condemn you back from where you came.
I got you. I got you.
You want to play games?
Okay.
Afraid to face me? Huh?
Helena.
Skip!
Hey.
Helena?
Fight it. Fight it, Helena.
Fight it. Fight!
They want me to go.
Yes.
What if I don't want to go?
A deal was made.
A life for a life.
Whose life?
Your father's for yours.
She loves him more than me.
Yes.
More than you.
More than me?
Susan.
- Bitch is mine!
- Megan! Megan!
Where is she?
I don't know.
Oh! What is... what is that?
- It's not her.
- What?
It has her.
- Rush her.
- What?
- Rush her, on three. One...
- Wait.
Two.
Three!
- Get her arms!
- Okay!
- Do you have any rope?
- Yeah, over there.
Get it.
Hurry up, Rob.
Take my place.
I'll be back.
You will kill her if you try.
Someone afraid to go for a little swim?
Humor in the time of death on the horizon?
Your death. You cannot hide
in her in the water.
Hide? I'm not hiding.
I'm ready to be in your world forever.
Don't you want to know where she is?
Don't talk to her.
Where is she?
- Close.
- Don't listen to her.
Don't listen to her.
Susan.
Susan!
She is mine! Me!
Thank you for your permission.
Permission?
- Permission?
- I didn't know!
It was the only way to save you.
I... I didn't... I didn't believe
the other part.
A house of lies.
Do they know your failures?
You will not take her.
Keep her under.
Close the door.
She's drowning.
She's okay. It'll leave her or die.
- Helena will die.
- No, she won't.
No.
Skip! Skip!
You're okay.
Rob?
I have to go see what's going on.
I'll be right back.
No! No, no.
Okay. Okay, we can go together. Okay?
Come on, I got you. Come on.
Rob?
Skip?
Up there.
There!
Skip?
Skip!
Ah! Oh, thank you.
You got this.
Come on.
Megan?
You sold me.
No, I didn't.
I didn't... I didn't think this was real.
You love him more than me.
No.
I love you both.
Okay, I'm going to get you out of here, okay?
No one is leaving.
She cannot kill until she is me.
And then you all will die.
No.
No. No!
- There we go. Let's go.
- Help me. Thanks.
No!
- Wait. It's a distraction.
- What?
- We need to go back to the house.
- No, Susan went up there.
No, it happens in the house.
It happens in the house.
- It just wants us to run around here.
- Let's go.
No, but Susan...
We don't have time. Come on, trust me.
Goddamn.
Susan!
I smell your fear.
You cannot have this child.
Are you her protector?
Yes.
And who will protect you?
- Come face us, demon.
- Am I to be afraid of you?
You are.
Why does the sensitive one not speak?
A vessel to trap, only not a speak of speak.
I have nothing to say to you.
Then you will not need your tongue
when I rip it out and feed it to you!
Helena?
Skip.
Oh, my God.
Helena!
No! Stop it!
Stop hurting her, please!
Helena?
Helena. Helena.
Get away from her!
Okay.
There you go. This should stop
the bleeding for now...
...till we get something better.
Something's wrong.
What? What are you talking about?
It can't be here.
There's not much time left.
It would have Megan here by now.
- But it happened here last time.
- It knows we know that.
It's a decoy.
Susan!
Susan.
Megan! Megan!
Susan!
No one can hear you.
You can scream if you like.
Susan?
She's here with me.
Susan, fight it!
Why fight destiny?
Susan, wake up! Megan! Megan!
Long have I waited to walk this earth.
Susan, fight it!
What an earth it will be.
Hurry.
Megan.
Hurry!
Oh, sensitive one...
...no final blood will be shed until after.
You cannot have her.
It's going to come out. Be ready.
Skip! Skip, what's happening?
I don't know.
Okay, if it doesn't come out,
then we have to stop it inside her.
Inside her? What does that mean?
I'm sorry, Rob.
It's the only way.
No! No!
- Don't let her go.
- She's... she's transferring!
It has to come out first.
It can happen without coming out.
We have to stop it, Skip!
We have to stop it! Skip!
Grab the stake.
- What?
- Grab the stake.
You have to kill it.
It's not out.
It's not coming out.
You have to kill it inside her.
No! No! No!
She's transferring to your daughter.
They'll both be dead if you don't.
- She'll walk this earth.
- No!
No! No!
You have to. I can't let her go and do it.
You have to do it. She's dead either way.
Do it!
You failed again.
- Skip!
- You can't have her!
- No!
- It's the only way!
Oh, God!
Skip.
Susan.
Oh, hey. Oh, hi.
Release her.
She vessel.
Please.
Please, release her.
You didn't live up to your deal.
Please.
Please, release her.
She will wander Limbo forever...
...because of you.
Oh, no. Oh, Megan!
Dad. Dad.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Oh, it's going to be okay.
- It's okay. It's okay, honey.
- Daddy.
It's okay.